{
    "question": "Arrange to a good sentences !    1)\u00a0realized - I - just - mistakes - had - we - made -\r\n2) they - when - gone - arrived - had - we - already\u00a0",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Maaf saya hanya bisa menyusun yang nomor 2, semoga membantu ya :)<br>2) We had already arrived when they gone.<br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "1. \"I realized mistakes we had made\" (saya menyadari kesalahan-kesalahan yang telah kita buat), or \"I realized we had made mistakes\" (saya menyadari bahwa kita telah melakukan kesalahan-kesalahan).<br>2. \"They had already gone when we arrived\" (mereka telah pergi ketika kita tiba), or \"We had alredy gone when they arrived\" (kita telah pergi ketika mereka tiba).<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "make-good-dialogues-expressing-feeling-and-attitude-based-on-the-373",
            "question": "Make good dialogues expressing feeling and attitude based on the following situations??    Hendra has a conversation with his mother in the evening. He tells her that he saw two black long plastic bags. He tought they were rubbish bags. When he came nearer, they were actually the corpse bags.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Mother: Good evening, Hendra<br>Hendra: Good evening, mom<br>Mother: Where have you been?<br>Hendra: I went to Ani&#039;s room to study together<br>Mother: Nice! Good boy..<br>Hendra: Umm...Mom, i have something to tell you<br>Mother: What is it?<br>Hendra: When on my way home, i saw a long and black plastic bag. I thought it&#039;s a rubbish bag. But when i came nearer the plastic bag, i smell a disgusting smell. So i open the plastic bag, and there&#039;s a corpse inside it! I was shocked, mom<br>Mother: Did you report it to the police?<br>Hendra: I have<br>Mother: Good boy, now\u00a0  let&#039;s have dinner<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mom: Welcome home darling! how was school?<br>hendra: well, if i have to be honest... not that good...<br>mom:\u00a0what happen hendra? come, take a seat and lets talk about this.<br>hendra: okay mom...<br>mom: so, tell me exactly what happen<br>hendra: when i was riding home with my motorcycle, i saw 2 black long plastic bags. i actually thought they were rubbish bag but when i came near it, they were actually bags full of corpse. i was so shocked earlier.<br>mom: my my... did u call the police?<br>hendra: yes i did mom, the policeman said that i did the right thing to call the police<br>mom: now thats my boy!\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bedanya-conditional-type-1-2-dan-3-320",
            "question": "Apa bedanya conditional type 1, 2 dan 3 ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "if conditional sentences? beda tenses-nya, sama fact-nya",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Type 1 = Real / Present Conditional (terjadi sekarang)<br>Form = If + S + V1..., I + will + V1...<br>Example = If I have money, I will treat you<br>Meaning = it may/ may not happen. Jadi artinya bisa terjadi atau tidak.<br><br>Type 2 = Contrary to the present fact (bertentangan sama yang terjadi pada kenyataan)<br>Form = If + S + V2..., I + would + V1...<br>Example = <br>a. If I <u>had money,</u> I would treat you<br>b. If I <u>were</u> you, I would leave him<br>Meaning = <br>a1. I don&#039;t <u>have money</u>, so I dont treat you, or<br>a2. I don&#039;t treat you, because I don&#039;t have money<br>b. I<u>&#039;m</u> not you, so I don&#039;t leave him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 2, penyataan dalam v2, arti dalam v1)<br><br>Type 3 <br>Form = If + S + had + V3..., I + would + have + V3...<br>Example = <br>a. If I had had money, I would have treated you<br>b. If my father had got marred again, my mother would have killed him<br>Meaning = <br>a. I didn&#039;t have money, so I didn&#039;t treat you<br>b. My father didn&#039;t get married again, so my mother didn&#039;t kill him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 3, penyataan dalam v3, arti dalam v2)<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expressions-of-surprise-untuk-dua-orang-622",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan \"Expressions of surprise\" Untuk dua orang?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dina : Hi dani did you know that everyone in this school is talking about you because\u00a0you are the winner of the sains olympiad?<br>Dani : Wow, what a surprise i can&#039;t believe it<br>Dina : Yeah you are the winner good job my friend<br>Dani : Thanks a lot dina<br>Dina : You&#039;re welcome dani",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-past-tense-menggunakan-used-to-712",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat past tense menggunakan used to",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "that scissors used my mom<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "contohnya : i used to studying at night<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bagaima-membalas-surat-kepada-pembeli-tersebut-kiara-agusta-jal-156",
            "question": "Bagaima membalas surat kepada pembeli tersebut??    kiara agusta\r\njalan W.Z Johanes No. 621\r\nThe Tiny Tots Toy Company\r\nJalan Kuningan Sari No. 50, Jakarta\r\nDear Costumer Service Respresentative,\r\n\r\nI recently purchased one of your Tiny Tents (Model #47485) for my three-year old daughter. Unfortunately, after viewing the components that came with the product, I discovered that four of the parts were missing. Also, the instructions that came with the tent are in portuguese and Russian, but not in english or french, the two languages I speak. These two unforeseen problems have resulted in the tent remeaning unassembled and unacceptable as a toy my daughter.\r\nI am writing to request replacements for the missing parts, and a copy of the full set of assembly instructions (in english or french) for the model I purchased. If reasonable arrangements are not made within ten bussines days, I will return the tent to the store I purchased it from and expect a full refund. To assist you in processing my request, I am including a copy of my sales receipt and a list of the missing parts.\r\nI have purchased other toys manufactured by your company in the past, and have always been impressed with the quality and selection that Tiny Tots has made available to its customers. I sincerely hope this is a one-time incident, and that any future purchases I make will live up to the standard my family has come to expect from your company.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nKiara Agusta",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Kiara Agusta,<br><br>I am glad that you let us know about this matter. We are more than happy to assist you and would like to keep you impress with our service. We apologize for the missing part of the screw which supposed to be attached to the tents. We will send it tomorrow. And also the copy of the instruction will be delivered together with these missing parts. Hopefully you are satisfied with our reply and always be our loyal customer<br><br>Regards<br><br>Toytots Representative<br>Laura <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggris-dia-mengernyitkan-alisnya-547",
            "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-gak-cara-menjawab-soal-bahasa-inggris-un-sma-dengan-902",
            "question": "Ada yang tau gak cara menjawab soal Bahasa Inggris UN SMA dengan trik tertentu supaya cepat dalam mengerjakannya.?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau mau mengerjakan soal bhs inggris dengan mudah ya kalu bisa tau artinya soal bhs inggris itu pasti tau jawabanya.....<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Perbanyak vocabulary, sering-sering ngelakuin latihan listening karena 20 soal pertama di UN SMA ngegunain metode ini. Perbanyak baca modul buat ngebantu. Ngulang soal yang sudah dikerjain. Dan terakhir do&#039;a minta kemudahan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-making-and-handling-cancellation-gimana-ya-ada-918",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan making and handling cancellation gimana ya?\r\nada yang bisa bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "David : Excuse me. I think there is a mistake in our bill. We didn&#039;t have dinner here lst night.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. Here&#039;s the bill from the hotel restaurant. It&#039;s got your signature on it.<br>David : But that&#039;s not my signature. I&#039;d like to speak to the manager.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. The manager is busy.<br>Manager : You have a complaint about your bill, sir ?<br>David : Yes. I&#039;m afraid there&#039;s a mistake. We didn&#039;t have dinner in the restaurant last night.<br>Manager : But this looks like your signature on the restaurant bill.<br>Let me see. Oh dear I&#039;m very sorry. There&#039;s another couple called Morris in the hotel.<br>They had dinner last night. Not you. I do apologize.<br><br>sudah ya cukup :)\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}